mrfdev.com 2018-07-08

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to me, I treat it like i would like mine to be treated. This privacy policy document explains when and how personal information may be collected. In any case, only non-personally identifiable information is collected, and I never sell, share, trade, or otherwise transfer personal information to third parties.

 **Browser Extensions**  
My browser extensions do not collect personal information, do not collect your browsing history, and do not track your browsing activity. They do not collect data of any sort, and they do not inject ads. Reviews that claim otherwise are posted by jealous developers who don't support that some of my browser extensions (more particularly [Enhancer for YouTube™](https://www.mrfdev.com/enhancer-for-youtube)) are featured in the Firefox Add-ons Gallery, the Opera Add-ons Gallery, and the Microsoft Store. All my browser extensions are manually reviewed by experienced developers before being distributed so if they were not complying with the different guidelines and policies ([Firefox Add-on Policies](https://developer.mozilla.org/Add-ons/AMO/Policy/Reviews), [Opera Publishing Guidelines](https://dev.opera.com/extensions/publishing-guidelines/#acceptance-criteria), [Google Chrome Web Store Developer Agreement](https://developer.chrome.com/webstore/terms) and [Developer Program Policies](https://developer.chrome.com/webstore/program_policies) for Chrome, [Windows App Developer Agreement](https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/legal/windows/agreements/app-developer-agreement) and [Edge Extension Policy](https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-edge/extensions/microsoft-browser-extension-policy) for Edge) they wouldn't pass reviews and would be rejected.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
I may use cookies and local storage to store non-personally identifiable information directly in your browser, such as your personal preferences when you visit my website. I use Google Analytics to analyse traffic on my website, and also use third party advertisements. Some of these advertisers may use technologies such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on my website, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) non-personally identifiable information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit my website, and in some cases, whether you have Flash® installed or not. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific websites you have visited. To learn more about how Google uses data when you use my website, visit [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/).

 **DoubleClick DART Cookies**  
I also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your browser when you are browsing the web and visit a website using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history. For example, if you have been viewing websites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related website, such as one about sport. DART uses non-personally identifiable information. It does not track personal information about you. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all websites using this advertising by visiting [https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com](https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/). To learn more about this practice or the possibility of prohibiting the use of such data by such companies, visit [http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). You should also consult the respective privacy policies of these third party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

You can also choose to disable or selectively turn off my cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with my website as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into your accounts. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a website running advertisements, a new cookie will be added to your browser. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at their respective websites.
